# **Fernando Ascencio**

UNITY, AR AND MOBILE DEVELOPER

## **Portfolio**



fhazel.com.mx

### Contact



+52 3334953311



fernandohazel1@gmail.com



Guadalajara, Mexico, Zapopan Jal.



fernandohab



<u>FernandoHazel</u>

# Languages

Spanish: English: Native Advanced

#### **Skills**

Git Unity

**NET MAUI** Scrum

C# **Firebase** 

**JavaScript** 

Node Js

Kotlin

Express js Swift HTML / CSS/ JS

React

SQL

#### **Education**

**Bachelor in Digital Animation** Tecnológico de Monterrey | January 2018 - December 2022

Videogame Developer Diploma Tec De Monterrey | February 2021 - May 2021

Full Stack Developer Diploma Digital House | April 2021 - August 2021

Unity Programmer Diploma Unity Technologies | November 2022

## About me

I am a 3 years experience developer which have worked in videogames, AR and mobile apps. My stack is Unity, Net MAUI, Kotlin, Swift and SQL but I started my coding journey with Nodejs and React before discovering my passion for mobile apps.

## **Professional Experience**

#### Mobile Game Developer

One Simple Game Guadalajara. JAL | February 2022 - August 2022

- Collaborated with designers to implement new mechanics using C# applying OOP and design patterns
- Created a fully responsive UI an UX experience with Unity canvas
- Documented code for better workflow
- Tested and fixed bugs resulting in a 90% reduction of bugs
- Added analytics sdk to track the user actions in the game
- Had daily scrum sessions to ensure a better team communication
- Used Git to ensure version control and safer workflow

#### **AR and Mobile Developer**

GSN Qro. Qro | November 2022 - May 2023

- Collaborated with product team to implement specifications using C#
- Consumed REST APIs with JSON and perfing CRUD to display, modify and store data
- Created a responsive UI and UX experience for IOS and Android
- · Used Git to ensure a better and safer workflow
- Tested and fixed bugs to ensure hight quality
- Created internal company apps for Grupo Bimbo, Ferromex and Silberhorn with unity for staff training and managment.
- Created an internal app with .NET MAUI for employees which improved the internal company efficiency and comunication

#### **Bussiness Owner**

Fhazel Solutions Tech | From December 2021

- Created responsive web sites for bussiness using HTML and CSS deployed with vercel
- Created multiplatform mobile app for a restaurant using .NET MAUI which improved user experience when buying food and drinks
- Creating and monetizing my own mobile games for Android and IOS using unity, one is already on production
- Creating and monetizing my own apps using Kolin and swift
- Applying Ad Mob, IAP and Firebase Analytics to monetize, track results and find bugs
- Updating youtube videos teaching others programming fundamentals and technologies curiosities
- I give private programming classes of Unity, Git, Nodejs and React
- · Working on a football club app with Kotlin and Swift
- Working on a transportation app with Kotlin and Swift
- Working on a football training app with Kotlin and Swift
- Leaded a team using scrum which published 2 videogames
- Ported a PC game to mobile and published it on google play